George Korson Collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1: Manuscripts
  - Subseries C: Correspondence
    - Correspondence, September 1952 (Box-folder 16/9)
    - Correspondence, October 1952 (Box-folder 16/10)
    - Correspondence, November 1952 (Box-folder 16/11)
    - Correspondence, December 1952 (Box-folder 16/12)
    - Correspondence, January 1953 (Box-folder 16/13)
    - Correspondence, February 1953 (Box-folder 16/14)
    - Correspondence, March 1953 (Box-folder 16/15)
    - Correspondence, April 1953 (Box-folder 16/16)
    - Correspondence, May 1953 (Box-folder 16/17)
    - Correspondence, June 1953 (Box-folder 16/18)
    - Correspondence, July 1953 (Box-folder 16/19)
    - Correspondence, August 1953 (Box-folder 16/20)
    - Correspondence, September 1953 (Box-folder 16/21)
    - Correspondence, October 1953 (Box-folder 16/22)
    - Correspondence, November 1953 (Box-folder 16/23)
    - Correspondence, December 1953 (Box-folder 16/24)
    - Correspondence, January 1954 (Box-folder 16/25)
    - Correspondence, February 1954 (Box-folder 16/26)
    - Correspondence, March 1954 (Box-folder 16/27)
    - Correspondence, April 1954 (Box-folder 16/28)
    - Correspondence, May 1954 (Box-folder 16/29)
    - Correspondence, June 1954 (Box-folder 16/30)
    - Correspondence, July 1954 (Box-folder 16/31)
    - Correspondence, August 1954 (Box-folder 16/32)
    - Correspondence, September 1954 (Box-folder 16/33)
    - Correspondence, October 1954 (Box-folder 16/34)
    - Correspondence, November 1954 (Box-folder 16/35)
    - Correspondence, December 1954 (Box-folder 16/36)
    - Correspondence, January 1955 (Box-folder 16/37)
    - Correspondence, February 1955 (Box-folder 16/38)
    - Correspondence, March 1955 (Box-folder 16/39)
    - Correspondence, April 1955 (Box-folder 17/1)
    - Correspondence, May 1955 (Box-folder 17/2)
    - Correspondence, June 1955 (Box-folder 17/3)
    - Correspondence, July 1955 (Box-folder 17/4)
    - Correspondence, August 1955 (Box-folder 17/5)
    - Correspondence, September 1955 (Box-folder 17/6)
    - Correspondence, October 1955 (Box-folder 17/7)
    - Correspondence, November 1955 (Box-folder 17/8)
    - Correspondence, December 1955 (Box-folder 17/9)
    - Correspondence, January 1956 (Box-folder 17/10)
    - Correspondence, February 1956 (Box-folder 17/11)
    - Correspondence, March 1956 (Box-folder 17/12)
    - Correspondence, April 1956 (Box-folder 17/13)
    - Correspondence, May 1956 (Box-folder 17/14)
    - Correspondence, June 1956 (Box-folder 17/15)
    - Correspondence, July 1956 (Box-folder 17/16)
    - Correspondence, August 1956 (Box-folder 17/17)
    - Correspondence, September 1956 (Box-folder 17/18)
    - Correspondence, October 1956 (Box-folder 17/19)
    - Correspondence, November 1956 (Box-folder 17/20)
    - Correspondence, December 1956 (Box-folder 17/21)
    - Correspondence, January 1957 (Box-folder 18/1)
    - Correspondence, February 1957 (Box-folder 18/2)
    - Correspondence, March 1957 (Box-folder 18/3)
    - Correspondence, April 1957 (Box-folder 18/4)
    - Correspondence, May 1957 (Box-folder 18/5)
    - Correspondence, June 1957 (Box-folder 18/6)
    - Correspondence, July 1957 (Box-folder 18/7)
    - Correspondence, August 1957 (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Correspondence, September 1957 (Box-folder 18/9)
    - Correspondence, October 1957 (Box-folder 18/10)
    - Correspondence, November 1957 (Box-folder 18/11)
    - Correspondence, December 1957 (Box-folder 18/12)
    - Correspondence, circa 1957 (Box-folder 18/13)
    - Correspondence, January 1958 (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Correspondence, February 1958 (Box-folder 19/2)
    - Correspondence, March 1958 (Box-folder 19/3)
    - Correspondence, April 1958 (Box-folder 19/4)
    - Correspondence, May 1958 (Box-folder 19/5)
    - Correspondence, June 1958 (Box-folder 19/6)
    - Correspondence, July 1958 (Box-folder 19/7)
    - Correspondence, August 1958 (Box-folder 19/8)
    - Correspondence, September 1958 (Box-folder 19/9)
    - Correspondence, October 1958 (Box-folder 19/10)
    - Correspondence, November 1958 (Box-folder 19/11)
    - Correspondence, December 1958 (Box-folder 19/12)
    - Correspondence, circa 1958 (Box-folder 20/1)
    - Correspondence, January 1959 (Box-folder 20/2)
    - Correspondence, February 1959 (Box-folder 20/3)
    - Correspondence, March 1959 (Box-folder 20/4)
    - Correspondence, April 1959 (Box-folder 20/5)
    - Correspondence, May 1959 (Box-folder 20/6)
    - Correspondence, June 1959 (Box-folder 20/7)
    - Correspondence, July 1959 (Box-folder 20/8)
    - Correspondence, August 1959 (Box-folder 20/9)
    - Correspondence, September 1959 (Box-folder 20/10)
    - Correspondence, October 1959 (Box-folder 20/11)
    - Correspondence, November 1959 (Box-folder 20/12)
    - Correspondence, December 1959 (Box-folder 20/13)
    - Correspondence, circa 1959 (Box-folder 20/14)
    - Correspondence, January 1960 (Box-folder 21/1)
    - Correspondence, February 1960 (Box-folder 21/2)
    - Correspondence, March 1960 (Box-folder 21/3)
    - Correspondence, April 1960 (Box-folder 21/4)
    - Correspondence, May 1960 (Box-folder 21/5)
    - Correspondence, June 1960 (Box-folder 21/6)
    - Correspondence, July 1960 (Box-folder 21/7)
    - Correspondence, August 1960 (Box-folder 21/8)
    - Correspondence, September 1960 (Box-folder 21/9)
    - Correspondence, October 1960 (Box-folder 21/10)
    - Correspondence, November 1960 (Box-folder 21/11)
    - Correspondence, December 1960 (Box-folder 22/1)
    - Correspondence, circa 1960 (Box-folder 22/2)
    - Correspondence, January 1961 (Box-folder 22/3)
    - Correspondence, February 1961 (Box-folder 22/4)
    - Correspondence, March 1961 (Box-folder 22/5)
    - Correspondence, April 1961 (Box-folder 22/6)
    - Correspondence, May 1961 (Box-folder 22/7)
    - Correspondence, June 1961 (Box-folder 22/8)
    - Correspondence, July 1961 (Box-folder 22/9)
    - Correspondence, August 1961 (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Correspondence, September 1961 (Box-folder 22/11)
    - Correspondence, October 1961 (Box-folder 22/12)
    - Correspondence, November 1961 (Box-folder 22/13)
    - Correspondence, December 1961 (Box-folder 22/14)
    - Correspondence, January 1962 (Box-folder 23/1)
    - Correspondence, February 1962 (Box-folder 23/2)
    - Correspondence, March 1962 (Box-folder 23/3)
    - Correspondence, April 1962 (Box-folder 23/4)
    - Correspondence, May 1962 (Box-folder 23/5)
    - Correspondence, June 1962 (Box-folder 23/6)
    - Correspondence, July 1962 (Box-folder 23/7)
    - Correspondence, August 1962 (Box-folder 23/8)
    - Correspondence, September 1962 (Box-folder 23/9)
    - Correspondence, October 1962 (Box-folder 23/10)
    - Correspondence, November 1962 (Box-folder 23/11)
    - Correspondence, December 1962 (Box-folder 23/12)
    - Correspondence, January 1963 (Box-folder 23/13)
    - Correspondence, February 1963 (Box-folder 23/14)
    - Correspondence, March 1963 (Box-folder 23/15)
    - Correspondence, April 1963 (Box-folder 23/16)
    - Correspondence, May 1963 (Box-folder 23/17)
    - Correspondence, June 1963 (Box-folder 23/18)
    - Correspondence, July 1963 (Box-folder 23/19)
    - Correspondence, August 1963 (Box-folder 23/20)
    - Correspondence, September 1963 (Box-folder 24/1)
    - Correspondence, October 1963 (Box-folder 24/2)
    - Correspondence, November 1963 (Box-folder 24/3)
    - Correspondence, December 1963 (Box-folder 24/4)
    - Correspondence, January 1964 (Box-folder 24/5)
    - Correspondence, February 1964 (Box-folder 24/6)
    - Correspondence, March 1964 (Box-folder 24/7)
    - Correspondence, April 1964 (Box-folder 24/8)
    - Correspondence, May 1964 (Box-folder 24/9)
    - Correspondence, June 1964 (Box-folder 24/10)
    - Correspondence, July 1964 (Box-folder 24/11)
    - Correspondence, August 1964 (Box-folder 24/12)
    - Correspondence, September 1964 (Box-folder 24/13)
    - Correspondence, October 1964 (Box-folder 24/14)
    - Correspondence, November 1964 (Box-folder 24/15)
    - Correspondence, December 1964 (Box-folder 24/16)
    - Correspondence, January 1965 (Box-folder 24/17)
    - Correspondence, February 1965 (Box-folder 24/18)
    - Correspondence, March 1965 (Box-folder 25/1)
    - Correspondence, April 1965 (Box-folder 25/2)
    - Correspondence, May 1965 (Box-folder 25/3)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), June 1965 (Box-folder 25/4)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), June 1965 (Box-folder 25/5)
    - Correspondence, July 1965 (Box-folder 25/6)
    - Correspondence, August 1965 (Box-folder 25/7)
    - Correspondence, September 1965 (Box-folder 25/8)
    - Correspondence, October 1965 (Box-folder 25/9)
    - Correspondence, November 1965 (Box-folder 25/10)
    - Correspondence, December 1965 (Box-folder 25/11)
    - Correspondence, January 1966 (Box-folder 25/12)
    - Correspondence, February 1966 (Box-folder 25/13)
    - Correspondence, March 1966 (Box-folder 25/14)
    - Correspondence, April 1966 (Box-folder 25/15)
    - Correspondence, May 1966 (Box-folder 25/16)
    - Correspondence, June 1966 (Box-folder 25/17)
    - Correspondence, July 1966 (Box-folder 26/1)
    - Correspondence, August 1966 (Box-folder 26/2)
    - Correspondence, September 1966 (Box-folder 26/3)
    - Correspondence, October 1966 (Box-folder 26/4)
    - Correspondence, November 1966 (Box-folder 26/5)
    - Correspondence, December 1966 (Box-folder 26/6)
    - Correspondence, circa 1966 (Box-folder 26/7)
    - Correspondence, January 1967 (Box-folder 26/8)
    - Correspondence, February 1967 (Box-folder 26/9)
    - Correspondence, March 1967 (Box-folder 26/10)
    - Correspondence, April 1967 (Box-folder 26/11)
    - Correspondence, May 1967 (Box-folder 26/12)
    - Correspondence, December 1967 (Box-folder 26/13)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 26/14)
    - Correspondence, 1960s (Box-folder 26/15)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box-folder 26/16)
  - Subseries D: Speeches and articles
    These are by George Korson unless otherwise noted.
    - Allentown chronicle and news articles - photocopies (1 of 4), 1931-1932 (Box-folder 27/1)
      Photocopies of cover and pages from original scrapbook album. The original scrapbook is in Box 82.
    - Allentown chronicle and news articles - photocopies (2 of 4), 1931-1932 (Box-folder 27/2)
      See the description for box-folder 27/1.
    - Allentown chronicle and news articles - photocopies (3 of 4), 1931-1932 (Box-folder 27/3)
    - Allentown chronicle and news articles - photocopies (4 of 4), 1931-1932 (Box-folder 27/4)
    - "America's anthracite miners: their ballads tell their story." Washington Post (photocopy), April 13, 1941 (Box-folder 27/5)
    - "Anatomy of a coal mine." Keystone Folklore Quarterly (photocopy), Spring 1963 (Box-folder 27/6)
    - "Anthracite ballads." Pennsylvania Arts and Sciences (photocopy), July 1938 (Box-folder 27/7)
    - "Anthracite miners as bards and minstrels." American Speech, December 1935 (Box-folder 27/8)
      Photocopy of the essay and the original issue of the journal.
    - Amish society: fulfillment and stress in the little community, by John A. Hostetler, circa 1963 (Box-folder 27/9)
      Book review (in typescript) by George Korson, with handwritten corrections.
    - Folklore for children and young people: a critical and descriptive bibliography, compiled by Eloise Ramsey with Dorothy M. Howard, 1953 (Box-folder 27/10)
      Two copies of a book review by George Korson, reprinted from Southern Folklore XVII: 3 (September 1953).
    - John Mitchell, miner, by Elsie Gluck (photocopy), April 24, 1929 (Box-folder 27/11)
      Book review by George Korson, published in Elizabeth Times.
    - Low bridge! folklore and the Erie canal, by Lionel D. Wyld, 1964 (Box-folder 27/12)
      Photocopy of book review by George Korson, published in Journal of American Folklore 77: 304 (April-June 1964).
    - The talking turtle, by Vance Randolph, 1958 (Box-folder 27/13)
      Photocopy of book review by George Korson, published in Keystone Folklore Quarterly 3: 2 (Summer 1958).
    - Time for fairy tales old and new, compiled by May Hill Arbuthnot, 1953 (Box-folder 27/14)
      Two copies of a book review by George Korson, reprinted from Southern Folklore Quarterly (December 1953).
    - A treasury of New England folklore, edited by B.A. Botkin, November 30, 1947 (Box-folder 27/15)
      Original clipping and photocopy of a book review by George Korson, published in The Washington Star.
    - A treasury of railroad folklore, edited by B.A. Botkin and Alvin F. Harlow, circa 1953 (Box-folder 27/16)
      Book review (in typescript) by George Korson.
    - A treasury of Slovak folk songs, edited by John J. Lach, 1951 (Box-folder 27/17)
      Book review by George Korson, reprinted from Notes 8:2 (March 1951).
    - What happened to Mother Goose, by Ray Wood, and Southern Illinois singing games and songs, by David S. McIntosh, circa 1940s (Box-folder 27/18)
      Review of two books (in typescript), by George Korson, on American Red Cross letterhead stationary.
    - "Bureau of Mines 50th anniversary." United Mine Workers Journal (typescript), November-December 1960 (Box-folder 27/19)
    - "A communication from folklorist George Korson." United Mine Workers Journal, January 15, 1965 (Box-folder 27/20)
    - "Courtship and marriage customs among the hard coal region Pennsylvania Dutch." Keystone folklore Quarterly (photocopy), Summer 1961 (Box-folder 27/21)
    - "Early history of the anthracite industry in Pennsylvania." The Pennsylvanian (two copies), April 1951 (Box-folder 27/22)
    - "Fifty years of growth and achievement by our union." United Mine Workers Journal (photocopy), January 15, 1940 (Box-folder 27/23)
    - "First-aid training is 50 years old in '60." United Mine Workers Journal, December 15, 1959 (Box-folder 27/24)
    - "Folksongs and ballads of the anthracite miners," October 9, 1964 (Box-folder 27/25)
      Speech given before the Pennsylvania Historical Association, Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania
    - "From the president's desk." Keystone Folklore Quarterly, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 27/26)
      One photocopy each from issues for Fall 1957, Winter 1957-58, Spring 1958, Summer 1958, Fall 1958, Spring-Summer 1959, and Spring-Summer 1960
    - "Henry W. Shoemaker: folklorist." Keystone Folklore Quarterly (photocopy), Spring 1957 (Box-folder 27/27)
    - "A history of the United Mine Workers of America." United Mine Workers Journal: typed manuscript (1 of 3), May 1965-July 1967 (Box-folder 27/28)
      The typed manuscript was received from King's College in two folders.
    - "A history of the United Mine Workers of America." United Mine Workers Journal: typed manuscript (2 of 3), May 1965-July 1967 (Box-folder 28/1)
      See note for box-folder 27/28.
    - "A history of the United Mine Workers of America." United Mine Workers Journal: typed manuscript (3 of 3), May 1965-July 1967 (Box-folder 28/2)
    - "A history of the United Mine Workers of America." United Mine Workers Journal: miscellaneous, May 1965-July 1967 (Box-folder 28/3)
    - "A history of the United Mine Workers of America." United Mine Workers Journal: research materials (1 of 3), May 1965-July 1967 (Box-folder 28/4)
    - "A history of the United Mine Workers of America." United Mine Workers Journal: research materials (2 of 3), May 1965-July 1967 (Box-folder 28/5)
    - "A history of the United Mine Workers of America." United Mine Workers Journal: research materials (3 of 3), May 1965-July 1967 (Box-folder 28/6)
      Handwritten notes from a loose-leaf binder.
    - "A history of the United Mine Workers of America." United Mine Workers Journal: illustrations, (photocopy) (Box-folder 28/7)
      The original has been relocated to box-folder 94/13.
    - "History of Wyoming Valley." Wilkes-Barre High School Journal, May-June 1917 (Box-folder 28/8)
    - "How Pat Dolan's speech started the 8-hour day." United Mine Workers Journal, April 1, 1939 (Box-folder 29/1)
    - "Humor of the anthracite miner." Pennsylvania Arts and Sciences (photocopy), Summer 1937 (Box-folder 29/2)
    - "Into the late of night the singing went on." New York Post, April 30, 1942 (Box-folder 29/3)
    - "Meet Philip Ginder - new hero of American folklore." Allentown Sunday Call Chronicle, November 13, 1955 (Box-folder 29/4)
    - "Minstrels of the mine patch." Labor Today, vol. 1, no. 4, September 1941 (Box-folder 29/5)
    - Miscellaneous newspaper articles, circa 1920s-1930s (Box-folder 29/6)
    - "Never underestimate an author's will to live," circa 1960s (Box-folder 29/7)
    - "The passing of the collier boy," undated (Box-folder 29/8)
    - "Pennsylvania German influence on the anthracite mining industry," circa October 21-22, 1955 and before (Box-folder 29/9)
      Includes copies of Korson's speech (in final and draft forms, as well as excerpts), plus two copies of the program from the 65th annual meeting of the Pennsylvania German Society, October 21-22, 1955.
    - "Red Cross spirit in action," October 19, 1945 (Box-folder 29/10)
      Speech given before the Red Cross Personnel Training Unit, The American University, Washington, D.C.
    - "A report on area redevelopment." United Mine Workers Journal, October 1, 1961 (Box-folder 29/11)
    - "Rich folklore uncovered for Pennsylvania folk festival." Bucknellian (original and photocopy), March 26, 1936 (Box-folder 29/12)
    - Speeches and scripts (miscellaneous), circa 1945-1965 (Box-folder 29/13)
      Some of the writings have been identified.
    - Speech, Booksellers' Association, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 5, 1949 (Box-folder 29/14)
    - Speech, Folklore Institute of America, Indiana University, Bloomington, Indiana, Summer 1958 (Box-folder 29/15)
      See box-folder 98/24.
    - Speech, Herodotan Society, King's College, Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, October 12, 1964 (Box-folder 29/16)
    - Speech, Little Theatre, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1936 (Box-folder 29/17)
    - Speech, Pennsylvania Folklore Society, University of Pennsylvania, May 3, 1958 (Box-folder 29/18)
    - Speech, Pennsylvania Federation of Historical Societies, May 15, 1948 (Box-folder 29/19)
    - Speech, Pennsylvania Society, May 5, 1965 (Box-folder 29/20)
    - Speech, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1938 (Box-folder 29/21)
    - Speech, Pottsville Shakespeare Club, Pottsville, Pennsylvania, 1938 (Box-folder 29/22)
    - Speech, Williamsport, Pennsylvania (Box-folder 29/23)
    - "The Story of anthracite and iron." United Mine Workers Journal, January 1, 1959 (Box-folder 29/24)
    - "My sweetheart's the mule in the mines." Two penny ballads and four dollar whiskey, (1 of 2), 1966 (Box-folder 29/25)
    - "My sweetheart's the mule in the mines." Two penny ballads and four dollar whiskey, (2 of 2), 1966 (Box-folder 30/1)
    - "Traditional minstrelsy being revived throughout Pennsylvania," circa 1936-1938 (Box-folder 30/2)
    - "What is folklore?" American Junior Red Cross News, February 1948 (Box-folder 30/3)
    - "The Williamsport Technical Institute story." United Mine Workers Journal, August 15, 1958 (Box-folder 30/4)
    - "Women technologists in the army," circa 1942 (Box-folder 30/5)
  - Subseries E: Manuscripts of published works
    In the King's College inventory this subseries was named "Manuscripts."
    - Songs and ballads of the anthracite miner, 1927 (Box-folder 30/6)
      Published by F. H. Hitchcock, 1927.
    - The miner sings: a collection of folk songs and ballads of the anthracite miner, 1936 (Box-folder 30/7)
      Published in 1936.
    - Pennsylvania folk songs and ballads for school, camp and playground, 1937 (Box-folder 30/8)
      Published in 1937
    - Minstrels of the mine patch: songs and stories of the anthracite industry: legal documents, circa 1938 (Box-folder 30/9)
      First published in 1938 by University of Pennsylvania Press.
    - Minstrels of the mine patch: partial manuscript, circa 1938 (Box-folder 30/10)
      See note for box-folder 30/9.
    - Minstrels of the mine patch: publicity, circa 1938 (Box-folder 30/11)
    - Minstrels of the mine patch: research notes (1 of 4), circa 1938 (Box-folder 31/1)
    - Minstrels of the mine patch: research notes (2 of 4), circa 1938 (Box-folder 31/2)
    - Minstrels of the mine patch: research notes (3 of 4), circa 1938 (Box-folder 31/3)
    - Minstrels of the mine patch: research notes (4 of 4), circa 1938 (Box-folder 31/4)
    - Black land: the way of life in the coal fields, circa 1941 (Box-folder 31/5)
      Published by Row, Peterson and Co., in 1941.
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: songs and stories of the bituminous industry: legal documents, circa 1943 (Box-folder 32/1)
      First published in 1943 by University of Pennsylvania Press.
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: manuscript 1 draft (1 of 3), circa 1943 (Box-folder 32/2)
      See note for box-folder 32/1.
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: manuscript 1 draft (2 of 3), circa 1943 (Box-folder 32/3)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: manuscript 1 draft (3 of 3), circa 1943 (Box-folder 32/4)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: manuscript draft (partial), chapters 2-8, circa 1943 (Box-folder 32/5)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: manuscript draft (partial), chapters 11-19, circa 1943 (Box-folder 32/6)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: manuscript of song texts, circa 1943 (Box-folder 33/1)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: manuscript (miscellaneous), circa 1943 (Box-folder 33/2)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: publicity, circa 1943 (Box-folder 33/3)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (1 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 33/4)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (2 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 33/5)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (3 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 33/6)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (4 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 34/1)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (5 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 34/2)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (6 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 34/3)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (7 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 34/4)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (8 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 34/5)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (9 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 34/6)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (10 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 35/1)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (11 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 35/2)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (12 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 35/3)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (13 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 35/4)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (14 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 35/5)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (15 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 35/6)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (16 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 36/1)
      See note for box-folder 32/1. Some papers in the original Box 65 was damaged in transit to AFC. After treatment by Conservation Division staff, they were rehoused in folders 36/1-7.
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (17 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 36/2)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (18 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 36/3)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (19 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 36/4)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (20 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 36/5)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (21 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 36/6)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (22 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 36/7)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (23 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 37/1)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (24 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 37/2)
    - Coal dust on the fiddle: research notes (25 of 28), circa 1943 (Box-folder 37/3)